shadesoflight.com 2008-09-14

# Shades of Light|Bath Lights Chandeliers Fans Floor Lamps Table Lamps Ceiling Lights Shades Sconces, Richmond, VA

## To our Customers: 

Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.  
Note, the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

_Shades of Light - Privacy Policy_  
Shades of Light is firmly committed to protecting your personal information and on-line security.

This site recognizes the IP addresses of visitors(AOL, MSM, Comcast etc), but not their personal e-mail addresses. Individually identifiable e-mail addresses are not captured or stored unless they are specifically provided by the customer. Persons who communicate with Shades of Light, and supply us with an e-mail address, may receive future communications by e-mail or telephone. Persons who do not wish to receive e-mail messages may contact Shades of Light and ask to be removed. Shades of Light supports a customer's right to "opt out." Email addresses are not sold or disclosed to any other parties.  
If any changes are made in the future to the Shades of Light Privacy Policy, the date the change was made and a brief description of the change will be listed in our privacy policy.  
Shades of Light's Privacy Policy is effective as of Monday, August 28, 2006.  
If you have any questions relating to our privacy policy, please feel free to send us a message at visitor@shadesoflight.com  
Your Personal Information: How it is used.  
Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like name and e-mail address). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitors' contact information (like e-mail addresses and credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the customer for products and services.

Shades of Light may disclose user information in order to identify, contact or bring legal action to person or persons causing injury or interference with the property or business practices of Shades of Light or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. We will disclose information in good faith when required to do so by law.

_Cookies & IP Addresses_  
Shades of Light's Web Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information.

• We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information.

• Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests.

• The use of tracking tools and cookies are industry standard—you’ll find them at most major web sites. We analyze data gathered by means of tracking tools and cookies only in the aggregate or for segments of our customer base, and not at the individual customer level. We do not include personally identifiable information, such as your name and e-mail address, in this analysis. Other than referring URLs, we do not follow your browsing path outside of shadesoflight.com.

 _Information Supplied to or Received from Third Parties_

E-mail addresses are not sold or disclosed to other parties.  
E-mail addresses are not exchanged with other venders for their "like product" e-mail campaigns, unlike our postal lists. In the event we decide to change this particular policy, you will receive notification of the proposed changes and will be given the option to "opt out" of such exchanges.  
To better serve you and to enhance your shopping experience, we may supplement the information listed above with data that is publicly available and with data we receive from other reputable sources whose privacy policies meet the Direct Marketing Associationrequirements.  
From time to time, we may share our Postal Mailing List with carefully selected providers of goods and services that may be of interest to you. (If you prefer not to receive mailings from these providers, you can notify us at any time.) Also, on rare occasions, we may disclose specific information upon governmental request in order to assist with fraud protection or investigation. Information is not provided to these agencies or companies for marketing or commercial purposes.  
In order to protect our customers' security to the fullest extent, information for all Shades of Light orders is filtered by a third-party screening application.  
We use a third party to facilitate our e-mail campaign transmission, and we can track open and click rates of e-mail campaigns.  
Shades of Light is not liable or responsible for the independent practices and/or privacy policies of other sponsors, merchants, affiliates, advertisers or other persons in correlation with our website. Shades of Light is not responsible for any email transmission errors that would prevent a customer from receiving an email from our company or if Shades of Light were not able to receive an incoming email from a customer.

_E-mail & Mailing Preferences_  
If you are currently receiving communications from Shades of Light, it is because you have notified us of your desire to receive these mailings, because you have recently requested products or services from us, or because you have provided information to a third party affiliated with Shades of Light. If you prefer not to receive catalogs, e-mail offers, or other communications from us, we give you the opportunity to terminate these mailings at any time. (Note: Because we plan our catalog and email mailings in advance, it may take several weeks for your request to become effective.)  
If you no longer wish to receive catalogs or mailings from affiliated companies, call 1-800-536-7551, send us a request by e-mail , or send your mailing label to:  
Shades of Light  
attn. Customer Service  
4924 West Broad St.  
Richmond, VA 23230

If you no longer wish to receive email offers, you may click on the "Unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any of our e-mails. (Note: Your selection will apply only to the current corresponding email address. Please allow up to 90 days for the activation of any changes in address status for postal mail and 10 days for e-mail. Future mailings may still be sent to alternate e-mail addresses you may have supplied to us. Also, you may still receive confirmation and/or tracking e-mails if you place an order on our website.)

_How to Remove Your Name from Mailing Lists, Telemarketing Lists and Email Lists in General_  
Most people enjoy receiving information about subjects that interest them or products and services they may need or want. Sometimes, however, the amount of this type of information we receive — by mail, phone or e-mail — can become overwhelming. Visit the Direct Marketing Association, Consumer Assistance site (www.dmaconsumers.org) to find out how you can get your name removed from these types of lists.  
Correcting or Updating Your Shades of Light Account Information  
• Call one of our Customer Service Representatives at 1-877-288-5029, ext. 319   
• Send an e-mail to unsubscribe@shadesoflight.com

_Children's Privacy Protection_  
The Shades of Light Web site is not intended for use by, nor do we knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 18.  
Disclaimer - Errors and Inaccuracies  
Occasionally, the information on shadesoflight.com may contain errors or inaccuracies related to product descriptions, product images, pricing, or availability. Though we make every effort to minimize these occurrences, Shades of Light is not responsible for errors or inaccuracies that occur as a result of human error, technical malfunction or other causes. We apologize for any inconvenience this may cause you.

|
